<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Food Express</string>
    <string name="resend_message">Resend SMS</string>
    <string name="profileTitle">Profile</string>
    <string name="member_name">Member name</string>
    <string name="contact_phone_no">Phone No</string>
    <string name="please_wait">Please wait</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="user_seller">Seller</string>
    <string name="user_customer">Customer</string>

    <string name="title_activity_splashscreen">SplashscreenActivity</string>
    <string name="dummy_button">Dummy Button</string>
    <string name="dummy_content">DUMMY\nCONTENT</string>

    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="menu_my_order">My Order</string>
    <string name="menu_last_order">Past Order</string>
    <string name="menu_new_order">New Order</string>
    <string name="menu_feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="menu_terms">Terms and Conditions</string>
    <string name="menu_contact">Contact Us</string>
    <string name="menu_logout">Logout</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>

    <string name="tnc"><![CDATA[<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:8.0pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><strong><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Arial&quot;,sans-serif;color:#282C3F;">FOOD EXPRESS STORES – USER TERMS</span></strong></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:8.0pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Arial&quot;,sans-serif;color:#282C3F;">This document is an electronic record in terms of Information Technology Act, 2000 and rules there under as applicable and the amended provisions pertaining to electronic records in various statutes as amended by the Information Technology Act, 2000. This document is published in accordance with the provisions of Rule 3 (1) of the Information Technology (Intermediaries guidelines) Rules, 2011 that require publishing the rules and regulations, privacy policy and Terms of Use for access or usage of <strong>Food Express Stores&nbsp;</strong>application<strong>&nbsp;(</strong>the <strong>“App / Platform”)</strong> for mobile and handheld devices.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:8.0pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><strong><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Arial&quot;,sans-serif;color:#282C3F;">Terms of Use</span></strong></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;These terms of use (the “<strong>Terms of Use</strong>”) govern your use of the Platform.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;The Platform is operated and owned by <strong>Bundl Technologies Private Limited (</strong>hereinafter referred to as<strong>&nbsp;“Food Express”)</strong>, a company incorporated under the Companies Act, 1956 and having its registered office at No. 17/9B, 4th Floor, Maruthi Chambers, Rupena Agrahara, Hosur Road, Bangalore – 560 068.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;For the purpose of these Terms of Use, wherever the context so requires, “you” shall mean any natural or legal person who has agreed to become a buyer by providing Registration Data while registering on the Platform as a registered user using any computer systems/mobile devices. The terms “Food Express”, “we”, “us” or “our” shall mean Bundl Technologies Private Limited.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;Please read these Terms of Use carefully before you use the services. If you do not agree to these Terms of Use, you may not use the services on the Platform, and we request you to uninstall the App. By installing, downloading or even merely using the Platform, you shall be contracting with Food Express and you signify your acceptance to the Terms of Use and other Food Express policies (including but not limited to the Cancellation &amp; Refund Policy, Return Policy, Privacy Policy and Take Down Policy) as posted on the Platform from time to time, which takes effect on the date on which you download, install or use the Services, and create a legally binding arrangement to abide by the same.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;Food Express Stores provides a Platform enabling transactions between the buyers and merchants dealing in various categories of products or services including but not limited to packaged food, dairy, vegetables, fruits, groceries, pharmacy, cosmetics, hardware and appliance, apparel and footwear, etc. You can (a) choose and place orders (“<strong>Orders</strong>”) from variety of products listed or catalogued and offered for sale by various neighbourhood merchants (“Merchants”) dealing in the categories of products or services listed in our Platform which shall be delivered by the concierge service provider (“Concierge”); (b) assign task such as purchase of products from the nearby stores or the listed Merchants and delivery of such products.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:8.0pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Arial&quot;,sans-serif;color:#282C3F;">Food Express enables the performance of such assigned tasks through third party service providers i.e. the Concierge at select localities of serviceable cities across India.&nbsp;To clarify, Food Express Stores is merely a technology platform and shall relay the assignments, either task(s) or order(s) to the respective Merchant and/or the Concierge to complete such assignments.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:8.0pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><strong><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Arial&quot;,sans-serif;color:#282C3F;">Account Registration or use of the Platform</span></strong></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;You may access the Platform by registering to create an account (“<strong>Food Express Stores Account</strong>”) and become a member (“<strong>Membership</strong>”); or (c) you can also register to join by logging into your account with certain third party social networking sites (“<strong>SNS</strong>”) (including, but not limited to, Facebook); each such account, a “<strong>Third Party Account</strong>”, via our Platform, as described below. The Membership is limited for the purpose and are subject to the terms, and strictly not transferable. As part of the functionality of the Platform services, you may link your Food Express Stores Account with Third Party Accounts, by either:</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;providing your Third Party Account login information to us through the Platform; or</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;allowing us to access your Third Party Account, as is permitted under the applicable terms and conditions that govern your use of each Third Party Account.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;You represent that you are entitled to disclose your Third Party Account login information to us and/or grant us access to your Third Party Account (including, but not limited to, for use for the purposes described herein), without breach by you of any of the terms and conditions that govern your use of the applicable Third Party Account and without obligating us to pay any fees or making us subject to any usage limitations imposed by such third party service providers.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;By granting us access to any Third Party Accounts, you understand that we will access, make available and store (if applicable) any content or information that you have provided to and stored in your Third Party Account (“<strong>SNS Content</strong>”) so that it is available on and through the Platform via your Food Express Account.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;Unless otherwise specified in these Terms of Use, all SNS Content, if any, will be considered to be your content for all purposes of these Terms of Use.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;Depending on the Third Party Accounts, you choose, and subject to the privacy settings that you have set in such Third Party Accounts, personally identifiable information that you post to your Third Party Accounts will be available on and through your Food Express Account on the Platform.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;Please note that if a Third Party Account or associated service becomes unavailable or our access to such Third Party Account is terminated by the third party service provider, then SNS Content will no longer be available on and through the Platform.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;We will create your Food Express Stores Account for your use of the Platform services based upon the personal information you provide to us or that we obtain via an SNS, as described above. You may only have one Food Express Stores Account and not permitted to create multiple accounts. If found, you having multiple accounts, Food Express reserves right to suspend such multiple account without being liable for any compensation.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;You agree to provide accurate, current and complete information during the registration process and to update such information to keep it accurate, current and complete.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;We reserve the right to suspend or terminate your Food Express Stores Account and your access to the Services (i) if any information provided during the registration process or thereafter proves to be inaccurate, not current or incomplete; (ii) if it is believed that your actions may cause legal liability for you, other users or us; and/or (iii) if you are found to be non- compliant with the Terms of Use.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;You are responsible for safeguarding your password. You agree that you will not disclose your password to any third party and that you will take sole responsibility for any activities or actions under your Food Express Stores Account, whether or not you have authorized such activities or actions. You will immediately notify us of any unauthorized use of your Food Express Stores Account.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;Products and services purchased from the Platform are intended for your personal use and you represent that the same are not for resale or you are not acting as an agent for other parties.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:8.0pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><strong><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Arial&quot;,sans-serif;color:#282C3F;">Specific Terms with respect to Use of Platform for purchase of Cigarettes and Other Tobacco Products&nbsp;</span></strong></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;You agree and undertake that You will not use the Platform to purchase cigarettes and other tobacco products if you are below the age of 18 years.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;The Concierge may request you to provide a valid age proof at the time of delivery of cigarettes and/other tobacco products, You agree and undertake to provide a valid age proof to the Concierge, if requested. If you fail to provide a valid age proof as requested by the Concierge, your order will be cancelled immediately.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;You agree and undertake that You will not use the Platform to place an order for loose cigarettes. Please note, only full packets of cigarettes can be sold by the Merchants through the Platform.&nbsp;</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:8.0pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><strong><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Arial&quot;,sans-serif;color:#282C3F;">Disclaimers</span></strong></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;THE PLATFORM MAY BE UNDER CONSTANT UPGRADES, AND SOME FUNCTIONS AND FEATURES MAY NOT BE FULLY OPERATIONAL.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;DUE TO THE VAGARIES THAT CAN OCCUR IN THE ELECTRONIC DISTRIBUTION OF INFORMATION AND DUE TO THE LIMITATIONS INHERENT IN PROVIDING INFORMATION OBTAINED FROM MULTIPLE SOURCES, THERE MAY BE DELAYS, OMISSIONS, OR INACCURACIES IN THE CONTENT PROVIDED ON THE PLATFORM OR DELAY OR ERRORS IN FUNCTIONALITY OF THE PLATFORM. AS A RESULT, WE DO NOT REPRESENT THAT THE INFORMATION POSTED IS CORRECT IN EVERY CASE.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;WE EXPRESSLY DISCLAIM ALL LIABILITIES THAT MAY ARISE AS A CONSEQUENCE OF ANY UNAUTHORIZED USE OF CREDIT/ DEBIT CARDS.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT THIRD PARTY SERVICES ARE AVAILABLE ON THE PLATFORM. WE MAY HAVE FORMED PARTNERSHIPS OR ALLIANCES WITH SOME OF THESE THIRD PARTIES FROM TIME TO TIME IN ORDER TO FACILITATE THE PROVISION OF CERTAIN SERVICES TO YOU. HOWEVER, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT AT NO TIME ARE WE MAKING ANY REPRESENTATION OR WARRANTY REGARDING ANY THIRD PARTY’S SERVICES NOR WILL WE BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY FOR ANY CONSEQUENCES OR CLAIMS ARISING FROM OR IN CONNECTION WITH SUCH THIRD PARTY INCLUDING, AND NOT LIMITED TO, ANY LIABILITY OR RESPONSIBILITY FOR, DEATH, INJURY OR IMPAIRMENT EXPERIENCED BY YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY. YOU HEREBY DISCLAIM AND WAIVE ANY RIGHTS AND CLAIMS YOU MAY HAVE AGAINST US WITH RESPECT TO THIRD PARTY’S / MERCHANTS SERVICES.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;FOOD EXPRESS DISCLAIMS THAT ALL LIABILITY THAT MAY ARISE DUE TO ANY VIOLATION OF APPLIBALE LAWS IN RELATION TO THE PRODUCTS OR SERVICES PURCHASED OR SOLD ON THE PLATFORM SHALL BE ATTRIBUTABLE TO THE MERCHANT.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;WHILE THE MATERIALS PROVIDED ON THE PLATFORM WERE PREPARED TO PROVIDE ACCURATE INFORMATION REGARDING THE SUBJECT DISCUSSED, THE INFORMATION CONTAINED IN THESE MATERIALS IS BEING MADE AVAILABLE WITH THE UNDERSTANDING THAT WE MAKE NO GUARANTEES, REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES WHATSOEVER, WHETHER EXPRESSED OR IMPLIED, WITH RESPECT TO PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATIONS, EXPERTISE, QUALITY OF WORK OR OTHER INFORMATION HEREIN. FURTHER, WE DO NOT, IN ANY WAY, ENDORSE ANY SERVICE OFFERED OR DESCRIBED HEREIN. IN NO EVENT SHALL WE BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY FOR ANY DECISION MADE OR ACTION TAKEN IN RELIANCE ON SUCH INFORMATION.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;THE INFORMATION PROVIDED HEREUNDER IS PROVIDED “AS IS”. WE AND / OR OUR EMPLOYEES MAKE NO WARRANTY OR REPRESENTATION REGARDING THE TIMELINESS, CONTENT, SEQUENCE, ACCURACY, EFFECTIVENESS OR COMPLETENESS OF ANY INFORMATION OR DATA FURNISHED HEREUNDER OR THAT THE INFORMATION OR DATA PROVIDED HEREUNDER MAY BE RELIED UPON. MULTIPLE RESPONSES MAY USUALLY BE MADE AVAILABLE FROM DIFFERENT SOURCES AND IT IS LEFT TO THE JUDGEMENT OF USERS BASED ON THEIR SPECIFIC CIRCUMSTANCES TO USE, ADAPT, MODIFY OR ALTER SUGGESTIONS OR USE THEM IN CONJUNCTION WITH ANY OTHER SOURCES THEY MAY HAVE, THEREBY ABSOLVING US AS WELL AS OUR CONSULTANTS, BUSINESS ASSOCIATES, AFFILIATES, BUSINESS PARTNERS AND EMPLOYEES FROM ANY KIND OF PROFESSIONAL LIABILITY.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;WE SHALL NOT BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANYONE ELSE FOR ANY LOSSES OR INJURY ARISING OUT OF OR RELATING TO THE INFORMATION PROVIDED ON THE PLATFORM. IN NO EVENT WILL WE OR OUR EMPLOYEES, AFFILIATES, AUTHORS OR AGENTS BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY FOR ANY DECISION MADE OR ACTION TAKEN BY YOUR RELIANCE ON THE CONTENT CONTAINED HEREIN.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:.0001pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:Symbol;">·</span><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Times New Roman&quot;,serif;">&nbsp; &nbsp;IN NO EVENT WILL WE BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DIRECT, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, SPECIAL, CONSEQUENTIAL OR EXEMPLARY DAMAGES, DAMAGES ARISING FROM PERSONAL INJURY/WRONGFUL DEATH, AND DAMAGES RESULTING FROM LOST PROFITS, LOST DATA OR BUSINESS INTERRUPTION), RESULTING FROM ANY SERVICES PROVIDED BY ANY THIRD PARTY OR MERCHANT ACCESSED THROUGH THE PLATFORM, WHETHER BASED ON WARRANTY, CONTRACT, TORT, OR ANY OTHER LEGAL THEORY AND WHETHER OR NOT WE ARE ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:8.0pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Arial&quot;,sans-serif;color:#282C3F;">If any of these Terms of Use should be determined to be illegal, invalid or otherwise unenforceable by reason of the laws of any state or country in which these Terms of Use are intended to be effective, then to the extent and within the jurisdiction where that term is illegal, invalid or unenforceable, it shall be severed and deleted and the remaining Terms of Use shall survive, remain in full force and effect and continue to be binding and enforceable.</span></p>
<p style="margin-top:0in;margin-right:0in;margin-bottom:8.0pt;margin-left:0in;line-height:normal;font-size:15px;font-family:&quot;Calibri&quot;,sans-serif;"><span style="font-size:16px;font-family:&quot;Arial&quot;,sans-serif;color:#282C3F;">&nbsp;(<em>Note: Food Express does not and cannot verify that Merchants have the right or ability to sell or distribute their listed products. However, Food Express is committed ensure that item listings do not infringe upon intellectual property rights of third parties once an authorized representative of the rights owner properly reports them to Food Express.</em>)</span></p>]]>
</string>

</resources>
